{
    "subject": "resource/Ra\u00fal_Garc\u00eda_(boxer)",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthYear",
    "object": "1982",
    "human_readable": "Ra\u00fal Garc\u00eda was born in 1982.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9817618131637573,
            "question": "Was Ra\u00fal Garc\u00eda born after the year 1980?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9658582210540771,
            "question": "Is Ra\u00fal Garc\u00eda's birth year before or after 1980?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8875806331634521,
            "question": "In what year was Ra\u00fal Garc\u00eda born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7864716649055481,
            "question": "What is Ra\u00fal Garc\u00eda's birth year?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7760209441184998,
            "question": "What century was Ra\u00fal Garc\u00eda born in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.732710599899292,
            "question": "What decade was Ra\u00fal Garc\u00eda born in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5712894201278687,
            "question": "How old is Ra\u00fal Garc\u00eda?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4903513491153717,
            "question": "Is Ra\u00fal Garc\u00eda a younger or older person?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4213353395462036,
            "question": "Ra\u00fal Garc\u00eda's birth year is a number higher than 1975. True or False?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3922688066959381,
            "question": "When did Ra\u00fal Garc\u00eda come into the world?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Ra\u00fal Garc\u00eda was born in 1982.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1388_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Ra\u00fal Garc\u00eda's birth year is a number higher than 1975. True or False?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1388_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Ra\u00fal Garc\u00eda a younger or older person?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1388_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How old is Ra\u00fal Garc\u00eda?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1388_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1388_106.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1388_111.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1388_112.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1388_118.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1388_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1388_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1388_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1388_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1388_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1388_96.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents state that Raul Garcia was born on September 10, 1982, which supports the query."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}